JAMES WOLFE

DETAIL

- o United States, Northern VA
- 0 (703)789-0919
- o Wolfe.James.J96@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/ja mes-wolfe-6420151aa/
- o https://jameswolfeblog.com

SKILLS

- Attention to Detail
- Effective Time Management
- o Teamwork and Communication
- o Organizational
- Computer Proficiency
- Web Development
- o Linux
- Agile

• PROFILE

Computer Science graduate with a passion for problem-solving and learning, demonstrated experience in programming and customer service. Developed technical skill sets required to thrive in a professional work environment, AWS Cloud, web development, Linux, and computer technology troubleshooting.

EXPERIENCE

Static Website Portfolios

January 2022 — Present

- Launched static website portfolios on AWS Cloud Services, Azure, Surge, and GitHub pages, developing and designing each using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Utilized key programs and services like S3, CloudWatch, Azure Container, GitHub, MobaXterm, and Trello gaining skills in Linx, Agile, and the Cloud.

Woodworker at Sue's Antiques, Manassas

June 2021 — Present

 Visit select antique shops around Northern Virginia refurbishing, refinishing, and selling 18th and 19th century antique furniture and items using sanding and stanning techniques.

Data Technician at CORESTAFF SERVICES, Haymarket

November 2020 — December 2020

 In a pair and independently resolved computer hardware issues on EC2 and S3 hosts after diagnosing, swapping, and reseating hardware components like the GPU, CPU, and RAM.

Restaurant Server at Mariachis TequliaRia & Restaurant, Manassas

June 2018 — January 2019

- In a fast-paced work environment, diligently served customers providing a high level of customer service while also managing time effective working independently.
- Developed skills in teamwork communication, attention to detail, and organization while preparing and serving customer food and drinks while providing quality service.

Sales Associate at PetValu, Manassas

September 2015 — August 2017

- Problem solved customer pet issues involving health and nutrition, and issues
 with cost or complicated problems involving pet travel, nail clipping, or toys.
- Worked independently and with a team developing excellent time management and multitasking skills in a fast-paced work environment.
- Volunteered working with dogs and cats at store events with Homeward Trails and German Shepherd Rescue and store kept pets as well as maintaining the health and containers of betta fish.

EDUCATION

Computer Science, Northern Virginia Community College, Manassas

September 2016 — May 2020

★ CERTIFICATIONS

Agile Scrum Fundamentals

April 2022

Linux Administration Bootcamp

March 2022

ude.my/UC-fcd5c324-ad8c-4b70-a83d-b9712cb3b0f8

AWS Cloud Practitioner

September 2022 — September 2023

7BEZSG02PNEEQ83D

CTECS National Readiness Skills

June 2015